The Observer Records UA062
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Observer article files, 1969 -- 1986; UA062.002; 3.6 Linear Feet
  - Braker Fire, 1970; UA062.002.005.00026 (Box 5)
  - Bookstore, 1970 -- 1975; UA062.002.005.00027 (Box 5)
  - B. S. O. T., 1972 -- 1982; UA062.002.005.00028 (Box 5)
  - Buben, Mark, 1979 -- 1981; UA062.002.005.00029 (Box 5)
  - Budget, 1979 -- 1980; UA062.002.005.00030 (Box 5)
  - Budgets, 1971 -- 1975; UA062.002.005.00031 (Box 5)
  - Budget, 1975 -- 1978; UA062.002.005.00032 (Box 5)
  - Budget, 1979 -- 1981; UA062.002.005.00033 (Box 5)
  - Budget, 1981 -- 1982; UA062.002.005.00034 (Box 5)
  - Budget Process, 1978 -- 1981; UA062.002.005.00035 (Box 5)
  - B & G, 1979 -- 1980; UA062.002.005.00036 (Box 5)
  - Cable TV, 1979 -- 1982; UA062.002.005.00037 (Box 5)
  - Cabot IC, 1980 -- 1981; UA062.002.005.00038 (Box 5)
  - Carpenter House Fire, 1979; UA062.002.005.00039 (Box 5)
  - Calendar, 1974 -- 1980; UA062.002.005.00040 (Box 5)
  - Cambodian Relief, 1979; UA062.002.005.00041 (Box 5)
  - Campaign for Tufts, 1977 -- 1982; UA062.002.005.00042 (Box 5)
  - Campus Center, 1975 -- 1981; UA062.002.005.00043 (Box 5)
  - Caps and Gowns, 1980; UA062.002.005.00044 (Box 5)
  - Career Guidance and Placement, 1972 -- 1982; UA062.002.005.00045 (Box 5)
  - Census, 1980; UA062.002.005.00046 (Box 5)
  - Chaplin, 1978 -- 1982; UA062.002.005.00047 (Box 5)
  - CHASM, 1970; UA062.002.005.00048 (Box 5)
  - Chemistry Labs, 1979 -- 1981; UA062.002.005.00049 (Box 5)
  - Child Study, 1973 -- 1974; UA062.002.005.00050 (Box 5)
  - Chinese/China, 1980; UA062.002.005.00051 (Box 5)
  - Chomsky, Noam, 1980; UA062.002.005.00052 (Box 5)
  - Church vs. State, 1980; UA062.002.005.00053 (Box 5)
  - Classics Department Curriculum, 1972; UA062.002.005.00054 (Box 5)
  - Class Size, 1978; UA062.002.005.00055 (Box 5)
  - Cohen (renovations), 1980 -- 1981; UA062.002.005.00056 (Box 5)
  - Associate Provost/Colcord, 1980; UA062.002.005.00057 (Box 5)
  - Cormack-1979 Nobel Prize, UA062.002.005.00058 (Box 5)
  - College Within, 1970 -- 1975; UA062.002.005.00059 (Box 5)
  - Commencement 1981, 1981 -- 1982; UA062.002.005.00060 (Box 5)
  - Committee on Social Responsibility, 1980; UA062.002.005.00061 (Box 5)
  - Committee on Social Review, 1980; UA062.002.005.00062 (Box 5)
  - Computers, 1974 -- 1981; UA062.002.005.00063 (Box 5)
  - Community Health Program, 1976 -- 1978; UA062.002.005.00064 (Box 5)
  - Community Relations, 1972 -- 1981; UA062.002.005.00065 (Box 5)
  - Construction Crisis (Volpe), 1970 -- 1974; UA062.002.005.00066 (Box 5)
  - Construction Problems, 1980; UA062.002.005.00067 (Box 5)
  - Continuing Education, 1970 -- 1974; UA062.002.005.00068 (Box 5)
  - Contraceptives, 1973 -- 1978; UA062.002.005.00069 (Box 5)
  - Copyright, 1977 -- 1978; UA062.002.005.00070 (Box 5)
  - Counseling, 1974 -- 1978; UA062.002.005.00071 (Box 5)
  - Course Evaluations, 1973 -- 1982; UA062.002.005.00072 (Box 5)
  - Cousens Gym Expansion, 1979 -- 1981; UA062.002.005.00073 (Box 5)
  - Crafts Center (Anthony House), 1979; UA062.002.005.00074 (Box 5)
  - Crime: Medford/Somerville, 1979 -- 1981; UA062.002.005.00075 (Box 5)
  - Criterion OPI, 1973 -- 1974; UA062.002.005.00076 (Box 5)
  - CSL, 1978 -- 1979; UA062.002.005.00077 (Box 5)
  - CSL, Observer Goof with, 1978; UA062.002.005.00078 (Box 5)
  - CSL, 1979 -- 1980; UA062.002.005.00079 (Box 5)
  - CSL, 1980 -- 1981; UA062.002.005.00080 (Box 5)
  - Curriculum, 1980 -- 1981; UA062.002.005.00081 (Box 5)
  - Dance, 1970 -- 1974; UA062.002.005.00082 (Box 5)
  - Davis Square, 1978; UA062.002.005.00083 (Box 5)
  - Day Care, 1970 -- 1974; UA062.002.005.00084 (Box 5)
  - Student Deaths, 1979 -- 1981; UA062.002.005.00085 (Box 5)
  - Debate Team (Forensic Council), 1970 -- 1978; UA062.002.005.00086 (Box 5)
  - Degree Requirements (including distribution, etc,), 1972 -- 1977; UA062.002.005.00087 (Box 5)
  - Dental Dean, 1978; UA062.002.005.00088 (Box 5)
  - Dental School, 1972 -- 1981; UA062.002.005.00089 (Box 5)
  - Department of Education, 1979 -- 1980; UA062.002.005.00090 (Box 5)
  - Development Division, 1979 -- 1981; UA062.002.005.00091 (Box 5)
  - Didio (Field Hockey Coach), 1979; UA062.002.005.00092 (Box 5)
  - Dining Services, 1972 -- 1981; UA062.002.005.00093 (Box 5)
  - Disabled Persons, legal compliance to, 1978 -- 1980; UA062.002.005.00094 (Box 5)
  - Divestment, 1977 -- 1978; UA062.002.005.00095 (Box 5)
  - Divestment, 1979; UA062.002.005.00096 (Box 5)
  - Divestment, 1979 -- 1980; UA062.002.005.00097 (Box 5)
  - Division of Colleges, 1980; UA062.002.005.00098 (Box 5)
  - Dorm Autonomy, 1972 -- 1980; UA062.002.005.00099 (Box 5)
  - Draft, 1979 -- 1980; UA062.002.005.00100 (Box 5)
  - Drinking Age, 1979; UA062.002.005.00101 (Box 5)
  - Dropping Courses, 1975 -- 1979; UA062.002.005.00102 (Box 5)
  - Drugs, 1970 -- 1979; UA062.002.005.00103 (Box 5)
  - Eating Places, 1980; UA062.002.005.00104 (Box 5)
  - Eaton Lounge, 1972 -- 1981; UA062.002.005.00105 (Box 5)
  - Economic Department, 1979; UA062.002.005.00106 (Box 5)
  - Education Department, 1971 -- 1974; UA062.002.005.00107 (Box 5)
  - Eliot-Pearson, 1978 -- 1981; UA062.002.005.00108 (Box 5)
  - Eliot (Dean), 1981; UA062.002.005.00109 (Box 5)
  - El Salvador, 1981; UA062.002.005.00110 (Box 5)
  - Endowment, 1978; UA062.002.005.00111 (Box 5)
  - Energy Crisis (see SOAP, PIRG, Environmental House), 1979; UA062.002.005.00112 (Box 5)
  - Engineering, 1971 -- 1982; UA062.002.005.00113 (Box 5)
  - Engineering Dean, 1978 -- 1980; UA062.002.005.00114 (Box 5)
  - English Department, 1979 -- 1981; UA062.002.006.00001 (Box 6)
  - Enrollment Predictions, 1978; UA062.002.006.00002 (Box 6)
  - Enrollment, 1980 -- 1981; UA062.002.006.00003 (Box 6)
  - Environmental House, 1980 -- 1986; UA062.002.006.00004 (Box 6)
  - EPC, 1970; UA062.002.006.00005 (Box 6)
  - ERA, 1981; UA062.002.006.00006 (Box 6)
  - Evelyn Wood, 1972; UA062.002.006.00007 (Box 6)
  - Expansion Plans, 1978 -- 1981; UA062.002.006.00008 (Box 6)
  - Faculty, 1979 -- 1982; UA062.002.006.00009 (Box 6)
  - Faculty Salary, 1974 -- 1981; UA062.002.006.00010 (Box 6)
  - Film Series, 1979 -- 1981; UA062.002.006.00011 (Box 6)
  - Fin Com (Financial Committee), 1980 -- 1981; UA062.002.006.00012 (Box 6)
  - Financial Aid, 1973 -- 1982; UA062.002.006.00013 (Box 6)
  - Fire Safety, 1979 -- 1980; UA062.002.006.00014 (Box 6)
  - Fiscal Year, 1978 -- 1979; UA062.002.006.00015 (Box 6)
  - Fletcher, 1978 -- 1981; UA062.002.006.00016 (Box 6)
  - Fletcher - Ciric, Funding Professors, 1971 -- 1986; UA062.002.006.00017 (Box 6)
  - Fletcher Dean Search, 1977 -- 1978; UA062.002.006.00018 (Box 6)
  - Fletcher Fire, 1970 -- 1972; UA062.002.006.00019 (Box 6)
  - Fletcher Tuition, 1979; UA062.002.006.00020 (Box 6)
  - FLY, 1970 -- 1974; UA062.002.006.00021 (Box 6)
  - Football, 1979 -- 1985; UA062.002.006.00022 (Box 6)
  - Foreign Study, 1970 -- 1982; UA062.002.006.00023 (Box 6)
  - Fraternity/Sorority, 1972 -- 1982; UA062.002.006.00024 (Box 6)
  - Freefer - How Observer Named Dorm, 1970; UA062.002.006.00025 (Box 6)
  - Frosh Writing, 1977; UA062.002.006.00026 (Box 6)
  - Gay Community, 1973 -- 1980; UA062.002.006.00027 (Box 6)
  - Graduation (Class of 1981), 1980; UA062.002.006.00028 (Box 6)
  - Graduation Speakers, 1979 -- 1981; UA062.002.006.00029 (Box 6)
  - Grants, 1980 -- 1986; UA062.002.006.00030 (Box 6)
  - Gesing, Steve (Student Activities Coordinator), 1979; UA062.002.006.00031 (Box 6)
  - Gittleman, Sol, 1981; UA062.002.006.00032 (Box 6)
  - Grad School (Tufts), 1974 -- 1977; UA062.002.006.00033 (Box 6)
  - Graduations (Early), 1970 -- 1974; UA062.002.006.00034 (Box 6)
  - Gynecologist, 1970 -- 1972; UA062.002.006.00035 (Box 6)
  - Hallowell, 1970 -- 1975; UA062.002.006.00036 (Box 6)
  - Harleston Report, 1978; UA062.002.006.00037 (Box 6)
  - Harleston Resignation, 1980 -- 1981; UA062.002.006.00038 (Box 6)
  - Health Services - General, 1979 -- 1981; UA062.002.006.00039 (Box 6)
  - Hemispheres, 1981; UA062.002.006.00040 (Box 6)
  - Hillel, 1971 -- 1979; UA062.002.006.00041 (Box 6)
  - Hillside Dorm, 1980; UA062.002.006.00042 (Box 6)
  - Hillside House, 1973 -- 1980; UA062.002.006.00043 (Box 6)
  - Hillside School, 1979; UA062.002.006.00044 (Box 6)
  - Hiring Practices, 1974 -- 1980; UA062.002.006.00045 (Box 6)
  - Hiroshima Survivors, 1980; UA062.002.006.00046 (Box 6)
  - Hoffmann, 1981; UA062.002.006.00047 (Box 6)
  - Hooper - Expansion, Workers, 1972 -- 1974; UA062.002.006.00048 (Box 6)
  - Hooper Incidents, 1976 -- 1979; UA062.002.006.00049 (Box 6)
  - Housing Crunch, 1978 -- 1980; UA062.002.006.00050 (Box 6)
  - Housing Director/Coordinator, 1978 -- 1979; UA062.002.006.00051 (Box 6)
  - Housing Policies, 1971 -- 1981; UA062.002.006.00052 (Box 6)
  - Housing Problems, 1970 -- 1977; UA062.002.006.00053 (Box 6)
  - Housing Problems, 1978 -- 1982; UA062.002.006.00054 (Box 6)
  - IDC, 1978 -- 1980; UA062.002.006.00055 (Box 6)
  - IDC, 1980 -- 1982; UA062.002.006.00056 (Box 6)
  - Intercultural Center, 1977 -- 1981; UA062.002.006.00057 (Box 6)
  - Internships, 1977 -- 1980; UA062.002.006.00058 (Box 6)
  - I.R. Department/Gibson, 1977 -- 1983; UA062.002.006.00059 (Box 6)
  - Iran/Iranian Students, 1979 -- 1980; UA062.002.006.00060 (Box 6)
  - ISP, 1975 -- 1978; UA062.002.006.00061 (Box 6)
  - Jumbo - Elephant, 1972; UA062.002.006.00062 (Box 6)
  - Kennedy, 1980; UA062.002.006.00063 (Box 6)
  - Knable, Bobbie, 1980 -- 1981; UA062.002.006.00064 (Box 6)
  - LATF, 1976 -- 1978; UA062.002.006.00065 (Box 6)
  - Leonard Carmichael Society, 1971 -- 1981; UA062.002.006.00066 (Box 6)
  - Levy, 1981; UA062.002.006.00067 (Box 6)
  - Libraries, 1981; UA062.002.006.00068 (Box 6)
  - Lincoln-Filene Center, 1972 -- 1975; UA062.002.006.00069 (Box 6)
  - Leach, Don, 1979; UA062.002.006.00070 (Box 6)
  - Liquor License, 1974 -- 1977; UA062.002.006.00071 (Box 6)
  - Loans, Student, 1980 -- 1981; UA062.002.006.00072 (Box 6)
  - MacPhie Pub, 1979; UA062.002.006.00073 (Box 6)
  - Majors, 1977; UA062.002.006.00074 (Box 6)
  - Manos, Steven, 1981; UA062.002.006.00075 (Box 6)
  - Marcos Gift, 1977 -- 1980; UA062.002.006.00076 (Box 6)
  - Master Plan, 1972 -- 1981; UA062.002.006.00077 (Box 6)
  - Matriculation (Class of 1984-85), 1980 -- 1981; UA062.002.006.00078 (Box 6)
  - Mayer, 1980 -- 1982; UA062.002.006.00079 (Box 6)
  - Mayer - pre-Tufts, 1976 -- 1982; UA062.002.006.00080 (Box 6)
  - MBTA/Red Line Expansion, 1979 -- 1980; UA062.002.006.00081 (Box 6)
  - MCATs, 1975; UA062.002.006.00082 (Box 6)
  - McCarthy Resignation, 1979; UA062.002.006.00083 (Box 6)
  - Meal Tax, 1974 -- 1978; UA062.002.006.00084 (Box 6)
  - Medford Square Renovation, 1977 -- 1978; UA062.002.006.00085 (Box 6)
  - Med (Medical) School, 1970 -- 1977; UA062.002.006.00086 (Box 6)
  - Med (Medical) School Tuition, 1978 -- 1979; UA062.002.006.00087 (Box 6)
  - Medical Aid for Indochina, 1972; UA062.002.006.00088 (Box 6)
  - Mental Health, UA062.002.006.00089 (Box 6)
    No Date Available
  - Military Recruiting, 1970 -- 1972; UA062.002.006.00090 (Box 6)
  - Minors, 1978 -- 1980; UA062.002.006.00091 (Box 6)
  - Minorities (see also, Hiring Practices, Steering Committee, Fraternity/Sorority, Racial), 1980; UA062.002.006.00092 (Box 6)
  - Mumford Plan, 1975 -- 1979; UA062.002.006.00093 (Box 6)
  - Murnane, 1979; UA062.002.006.00094 (Box 6)
  - Murrow, Edward R. Center, 1971 -- 1974; UA062.002.006.00095 (Box 6)
  - Music Department, 1974 -- 1981; UA062.002.006.00096 (Box 6)
  - New England Conservatory (Joint Program), 1979; UA062.002.006.00097 (Box 6)
  - New Dorm/Latin Way, 1979 -- 1980; UA062.002.006.00098 (Box 6)
  - New Dorm (Medford), 1978 -- 1980; UA062.002.006.00099 (Box 6)
  - NESCAC, 1978; UA062.002.006.00100 (Box 6)
  - NLRB, 1979; UA062.002.006.00101 (Box 6)
  - North Hall Blaze, 1972; UA062.002.006.00102 (Box 6)
  - Nutrition Center, 1977 -- 1978; UA062.002.006.00103 (Box 6)
  - Nuclear Power, 1979 -- 1981; UA062.002.006.00104 (Box 6)
  - Observer Stops Publication, 1971; UA062.002.006.00105 (Box 6)
  - Observer - Staff Collective, 1972 -- 1981; UA062.002.006.00106 (Box 6)
  - Oceanic Institute, 1978; UA062.002.006.00107 (Box 6)
  - Off-Campus Housing, 1970 -- 1980; UA062.002.006.00108 (Box 6)
  - Office of Equal Opportunity, 1980 -- 1981; UA062.002.006.00109 (Box 6)
  - Olympics, 1980; UA062.002.006.00110 (Box 6)
  - Optics Institute, 1977; UA062.002.006.00111 (Box 6)
  - Oxfam, 1981; UA062.002.006.00112 (Box 6)
  - Parking, 1972 -- 1981; UA062.002.006.00113 (Box 6)
  - Pass/Fail, 1973 -- 1975; UA062.002.006.00114 (Box 6)
  - Personnel, 1980 -- 1982; UA062.002.006.00115 (Box 6)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1972; UA062.002.006.00116 (Box 6)
  - Phone Systems, 1975 -- 1979; UA062.002.006.00117 (Box 6)
  - Physical Plant, 1980; UA062.002.006.00118 (Box 6)
  - Pig Book, 1974; UA062.002.006.00119 (Box 6)
  - Pinball, 1977 -- 1979; UA062.002.006.00120 (Box 6)
  - PIRG, 1978 -- 1983; UA062.002.006.00121 (Box 6)
  - Plan of Study, 1976; UA062.002.007.00001 (Box 7)
  - PLO, 1980; UA062.002.007.00002 (Box 7)
  - Police - Personnel hired, funds, 1973 -- 1980; UA062.002.007.00003 (Box 7)
  - Poli Sci (Political Science) Curriculum, 1972 -- 1975; UA062.002.007.00004 (Box 7)
  - Politics, 1981; UA062.002.007.00005 (Box 7)
  - Preceptors, 1977 -- 1979; UA062.002.007.00006 (Box 7)
  - Pre-registration, 1980; UA062.002.007.00007 (Box 7)
  - Presidential Election, 1980; UA062.002.007.00008 (Box 7)
  - Prexy Search, 1975 -- 1976; UA062.002.007.00009 (Box 7)
  - Princeton Plan, 1980 -- 1981; UA062.002.007.00010 (Box 7)
  - Program Plan Summary, 1980 -- 1981; UA062.002.007.00011 (Box 7)
  - Proposition 2.5, 1980; UA062.002.007.00012 (Box 7)
  - Provost - position and interim, 1979 -- 1981; UA062.002.007.00013 (Box 7)
  - PUSEP, 1979; UA062.002.007.00014 (Box 7)
  - Railroad at Tufts, 1977; UA062.002.007.00015 (Box 7)
  - Ramirez (Gilma), 1978; UA062.002.007.00016 (Box 7)
  - Rape Cases, 1972 -- 1981; UA062.002.007.00017 (Box 7)
  - Reaccreditation, 1980 -- 1981; UA062.002.007.00018 (Box 7)
  - Reagan (President), 1980 -- 1981; UA062.002.007.00019 (Box 7)
  - Recycling, 1978 -- 1980; UA062.002.007.00020 (Box 7)
  - Registration, 1981 -- 1982; UA062.002.007.00021 (Box 7)
  - Rent Control, 1978; UA062.002.007.00022 (Box 7)
  - Report to Trustees, 1977; UA062.002.007.00023 (Box 7)
  - Residential Staff, 1981; UA062.002.007.00024 (Box 7)
  - Resources, 1978 -- 1979; UA062.002.007.00025 (Box 7)
  - Resources (resignation), 1979 -- 1980; UA062.002.007.00026 (Box 7)
  - Racial Issues (see also: Steering Committee, Fraternity/Sorority, Minorities), 1980 -- 1981; UA062.002.007.00027 (Box 7)
  - ROTC (see Title 9), 1972 -- 1981; UA062.002.007.00028 (Box 7)
  - Russian Dancers, 1978 -- 1979; UA062.002.007.00029 (Box 7)
  - Safety Officer, 1979 -- 1980; UA062.002.007.00030 (Box 7)
  - Sailing/Sailors, 1979 -- 1981; UA062.002.007.00031 (Box 7)
  - Salt 2 (general information), 1979; UA062.002.007.00032 (Box 7)
  - Schmidt (Chancellor of West Germany), 1980; UA062.002.007.00033 (Box 7)
  - Security, 1970 -- 1974; UA062.002.007.00034 (Box 7)
  - Security, 1978 -- 1979; UA062.002.007.00035 (Box 7)
  - Sex Bias Cases, 1974 -- 1980; UA062.002.007.00036 (Box 7)
  - Student Senate, 1978 -- 1979; UA062.002.007.00037 (Box 7)
  - Security, 1979 -- 1982; UA062.002.007.00038 (Box 7)
  - Student Senate, 1979 -- 1980; UA062.002.007.00039 (Box 7)
  - Student Senate, 1980 -- 1981; UA062.002.007.00040 (Box 7)
  - Senate, 1981 -- 1982; UA062.002.007.00041 (Box 7)
  - Sheraton Commander, 1977 -- 1980; UA062.002.007.00042 (Box 7)
  - Shuttle - Commander to Tufts, 1977 -- 1981; UA062.002.007.00043 (Box 7)
  - Shuttle - Lesley to Tufts, 1973; UA062.002.007.00044 (Box 7)
  - Shuttle - TNEMC to Tufts, 1972 -- 1981; UA062.002.007.00045 (Box 7)
  - SOAP (see PIRG), 1970 -- 1974; UA062.002.007.00046 (Box 7)
  - Sociology/Anthropology, 1972 -- 1973; UA062.002.007.00047 (Box 7)
  - Somerville asks for money, 1972 -- 1981; UA062.002.007.00048 (Box 7)
  - Somerville fails in try to tax Tufts University dorms, 1974; UA062.002.007.00049 (Box 7)
  - Sophomore Standing, 1976; UA062.002.007.00050 (Box 7)
  - Soviet Students, 1975; UA062.002.007.00051 (Box 7)
  - Speakers, 1980 -- 1981; UA062.002.007.00052 (Box 7)
  - SPIRT, 1979 -- 1981; UA062.002.007.00053 (Box 7)
  - Steering Committee/Racial Tension, 1971 -- 1974; UA062.002.007.00054 (Box 7)
  - Student Activity Fee, 1971 -- 1980; UA062.002.007.00055 (Box 7)
  - Student Activities Office, 1980 -- 1981; UA062.002.007.00056 (Box 7)
  - Student File Laws, 1974 -- 1981; UA062.002.007.00057 (Box 7)
  - Student Resource Center, 1976; UA062.002.007.00058 (Box 7)
  - Sununu (John), 1979 -- 1981; UA062.002.007.00059 (Box 7)
  - Surplus/Deficit Policy, 1981; UA062.002.007.00060 (Box 7)
  - Swimming, 1981; UA062.002.007.00061 (Box 7)
  - TA's (teaching assistants), 1977; UA062.002.007.00062 (Box 7)
  - Talloires, 1977 -- 1979; UA062.002.007.00063 (Box 7)
  - TCA: Cooperative Agencies (See also: Today Tufts), 1979 -- 1980; UA062.002.007.00064 (Box 7)
  - TCB (Tufts Center/Concert Board), 1972 -- 1979; UA062.002.007.00065 (Box 7)
  - TEAC (See Recycling, Environmental House), 1981; UA062.002.007.00066 (Box 7)
  - TEMT, 1981; UA062.002.007.00067 (Box 7)
  - Tenure and Promotion, 1972 -- 1981; UA062.002.007.00068 (Box 7)
  - Term Papers, 1972 -- 1974; UA062.002.007.00069 (Box 7)
  - THAP, 1980; UA062.002.007.00070 (Box 7)
  - Theft, 1969 -- 1980; UA062.002.007.00071 (Box 7)
  - Title 9 (law against sex bias in education), 1978 -- 1982; UA062.002.007.00072 (Box 7)
  - Today Tufts, 1977 -- 1980; UA062.002.007.00073 (Box 7)
  - Traffic Commission, 1973 -- 1975; UA062.002.007.00074 (Box 7)
  - TSR, 1980; UA062.002.007.00075 (Box 7)
  - TPAC, 1978; UA062.002.007.00076 (Box 7)
  - Transfer Students, 1975 -- 1981; UA062.002.007.00077 (Box 7)
  - Tripartite Board, 1970 -- 1979; UA062.002.007.00078 (Box 7)
  - Trustees, 1974 -- 1981; UA062.002.007.00079 (Box 7)
  - Tufts in Washington, 1975; UA062.002.007.00080 (Box 7)
  - Tufts Daily, 1980; UA062.002.007.00081 (Box 7)
  - Tuition Protest, 1979; UA062.002.007.00082 (Box 7)
  - Tuition, 1979 -- 1981; UA062.002.007.00083 (Box 7)
  - Tutoring, 1970 -- 1974; UA062.002.007.00084 (Box 7)
  - TUTV, 1977 -- 1979; UA062.002.007.00085 (Box 7)
  - Union - Local 925, 1979 -- 1980; UA062.002.007.00086 (Box 7)
  - Upward Bound, 1970 -- 1971; UA062.002.007.00087 (Box 7)
  - Voting (U. S. local), 1971 -- 1974; UA062.002.007.00088 (Box 7)
  - Vet School, 1978 -- 1982; UA062.002.007.00089 (Box 7)
  - Walnut Hill Corporation, 1973; UA062.002.007.00090 (Box 7)
  - Wage Price Freeze 1971 - effect on Tufts, UA062.002.007.00091 (Box 7)
  - Wells (William), 1980; UA062.002.007.00092 (Box 7)
  - Wessell, 1977 -- 1981; UA062.002.007.00093 (Box 7)
  - Winart (See Student Senate 1978-1979, Security), 1977 -- 1979; UA062.002.007.00094 (Box 7)
  - Winter 1973-1974 (Short semester energy crisis), UA062.002.007.00095 (Box 7)
  - Winter Study, 1970 -- 1974; UA062.002.007.00096 (Box 7)
  - Winthrop Street, 1979 -- 1981; UA062.002.007.00097 (Box 7)
  - Women - Overview articles (See Title 9, Rape, Gynecologist), 1971 -- 1981; UA062.002.007.00098 (Box 7)
  - Women's Center, 1972 -- 1981; UA062.002.007.00099 (Box 7)
  - WMFO (See Student Senate), 1971 -- 1981; UA062.002.007.00100 (Box 7)
  - World Food Crisis, 1980 -- 1981; UA062.002.007.00101 (Box 7)
  - Yeager (Charles), 1973; UA062.002.007.00102 (Box 7)
  - YRO (Year Round Operation), 1974 -- 1975; UA062.002.007.00103 (Box 7)
  - A, 1985 -- 1986; UA062.002.007.00104 (Box 7)
  - C, 1985 -- 1986; UA062.002.007.00105 (Box 7)
  - D, 1985 -- 1986; UA062.002.007.00106 (Box 7)
  - E, 1985 -- 1986; UA062.002.007.00107 (Box 7)
  - F, 1985 -- 1986; UA062.002.007.00108 (Box 7)
  - G, 1985 -- 1986; UA062.002.007.00109 (Box 7)
  - H, 1985 -- 1986; UA062.002.007.00110 (Box 7)
  - I, 1985 -- 1986; UA062.002.007.00111 (Box 7)
  - J-K, 1985 -- 1986; UA062.002.007.00112 (Box 7)
  - L, 1985 -- 1986; UA062.002.007.00113 (Box 7)
  - M, 1985 -- 1986; UA062.002.007.00114 (Box 7)
  - N, 1985 -- 1986; UA062.002.007.00115 (Box 7)
  - P, 1985 -- 1986; UA062.002.007.00116 (Box 7)
  - Q, R, 1985 -- 1986; UA062.002.007.00117 (Box 7)
  - S, 1985 -- 1986; UA062.002.007.00118 (Box 7)
  - T, 1985 -- 1986; UA062.002.007.00119 (Box 7)
  - U-V, 1985 -- 1986; UA062.002.007.00120 (Box 7)
  - W-Z, 1985 -- 1986; UA062.002.007.00121 (Box 7)
- Observer research files, 1968 -- 1982; UA062.003; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series contains research files on topics including government agencies, university budget, legal disputes, people, student senate, student resources. Types of materials include: legal documents, newspaper clippings, planning documents, reports, copies of FBI materials available through the Freedom of Information Act. This series also contains organizational information about the Observer and graphics (cartoons) published by the Observer. Cartoons are organized by general topics, and individual cartoons are cross-referenced to particular article files.
  - Affirmative Action, UA062.003.008.00001 (Box 8)
  - Budget, 1981; UA062.003.008.00002 (Box 8)
  - Budget, 1982; UA062.003.008.00003 (Box 8)
  - Carton, Lonnie versus Tufts, 1981; UA062.003.008.00004 (Box 8)
  - CIA, 1972 -- 1979; UA062.003.008.00005 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, 1979 -- 1981; UA062.003.008.00006 (Box 8)
  - Facilities for the Arts, 1981; UA062.003.008.00007 (Box 8)
  - FBI/CIA (1 of 2), 1976 -- 1981; UA062.003.008.00008 (Box 8)
  - FBI/CIA (2 of 2), 1981; UA062.003.008.00009 (Box 8)
  - FBI, 1968 -- 1981; UA062.003.008.00010 (Box 8)
  - Finance Committee, 1981; UA062.003.008.00011 (Box 8)
  - Graphics - Administration, UA062.003.008.00012 (Box 8)
  - Graphics - Campus, UA062.003.008.00013 (Box 8)
  - Graphics - Miscellaneous, UA062.003.008.00014 (Box 8)
  - Graphics - Politics, UA062.003.008.00015 (Box 8)
  - Graphics - Student Life, UA062.003.008.00016 (Box 8)
  - Mayer, Jean, 1976 -- 1982; UA062.003.008.00017 (Box 8)
  - Organizational Information (Observer), 1981; UA062.003.008.00018 (Box 8)
  - Reilly, John T. - Deposition, 1978 -- 1980; UA062.003.008.00019 (Box 8)
  - Senate, 1980 -- 1982; UA062.003.008.00020 (Box 8)
  - TSR (Tufts Student Resources), 1980 -- 1981; UA062.003.008.00021 (Box 8)
  - Vey, Robert J., 1980 -- 1981; UA062.003.008.00022 (Box 8)
- Observer negatives, 1972 -- 1989; 1980 -- 1989; UA062.004; 2.65 Linear Feet; 13 Digital Object(s)
  This series contains photo negatives and some contact sheets from the Observer. Subject headings include sites on and off campus, issues and events, faculty and staff, students, sports, and speakers.
  This series is arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - (A), 1972 -- 1983; UA062.004.009.00001 (Box 9)
    Students Who Spent Year Abroad (A-C): 9/28/83, Paul Ford; Anti Draft Speaker (A-B): Karen Edensword; African Drum Ensemble A-3 (A-B): S. Morisseau; Assorted Negatives (A-C): 10/6/82, Allen Levenson; Apple Jam: 5/3/82, A. Levenson; Administrators: 3/17/82, A. Levenson; Anorexia: 3/3/82, Allen Levenson; Auto Accident (A-C): 2/79.
  - (A), 1986 -- 1987; UA062.004.009.00002 (Box 9)
    Army and Hellicopters: 10/1/87,C50 Steve Bushell; Athletics: 4/86, Chuck Boat-Wright; Tufts Arena Theater: 10/30/87, Tina Daley; Asian Basketball: 4/7/87, Steven Bushell; Aquarium: 4/7/87, Steven Bushell; Aerobics (A-B): 2/26/86, Alison Feriante; After Hours: 11/12/87, Steve Bushell
  - Arena Theater, 1981 -- 1982; UA062.004.009.00003 (Box 9)
    Best Man (A-C): 10/27/82, Ireman; Cecil- The Play (A-B): 11/3/81, Allen Levenson; Big and Little: no date.
  - Arena Theater, 1981 -- 1984; UA062.004.009.00004 (Box 9)
    Lodgehouse Blues (A-B): 12/7/81, K. Edensword; Lower Depths (A-B): 4/26/84, Ken McGagh
  - Arena Theater, 1980 -- 1985; UA062.004.009.00005 (Box 9)